amazing-animations.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy - Amazing-animations.com

This notice provides Amazing-Animations.com's policy regarding the nature, purpose, use and sharing of any information collected via this Web site. 

Submitting information is strictly voluntary. By doing so, you are giving Amazing-Animations.com your permission to use the information for the intended purpose. 

There are several types of information we collect. These include: 

Automatically Collected Information  
We collect and temporarily store certain technical information about your visit for use in site management and security purposes. This information includes:  
The date and time you access Amazing-Animations.com  
The URLs of the pages you visit  
The Internet domain from which you access Amazing-Animations.com.  
The IP address from which you access Amazing-Animations.com  
The type of browser used to access our site.  
The operating system used to access our site.  
If you visited this Web site from another Web site, the URL of the forwarding site.  
This information is only used to help us make our site more useful for you. With this data we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. 

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are retained temporarily as required for security and site management purposes only. 

Advertising  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/>.

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google�s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (�interest based targeting�). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses �non personally identifiable information�. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>. 

For more information on the types of cookies used by Google, go to the site "Types of cookies used by Google," located at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/types>, or any other URL Google may provide from time to time. For more information on Google Analytics, and how it collects and processes data visit the site "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or Apps," located at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>.

Cookies  
Amazing-Animations.com Web sites may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site. 

At no time is your private information, whether stored in persistent cookies or elsewhere, shared with third parties who have no right to that information. If you do not wish to have session or persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser. 

Personal Information  
If you choose to provide us with personal information, through such methods as completing a form or sending us an email, we will use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information or services you have requested. 

Accessibility Statement  
We continually strive to ensure the pages on this Web site are accessible to individuals with disabilities in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act. If you have any difficulty viewing any page with adaptive technology, please contact the webmaster. 

Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement  
Amazing-Animations.com links to many Web sites. Amazing-Animations.com provides links to these sites as a service to our users. The presence of a link is not a Amazing-Animations.com endorsement of the site. 

When users follow a link to an outside Web site, they are leaving Amazing-Animations.com and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the owners/sponsors of the outside Web site(s). Amazing-Animations.com is not responsible for the information collection practices of those sites. 

How Your Information May Be Used

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of the Website, and customize the Website for your account; 
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

Rights Related To Your Personal Information

Opt-out � You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us using the email address below.

Amend � You may contact us to amend or update your personal information.

Forget � In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to the email address below.

Access � You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to [webmaster@Amazing-Animations.com](mailto:webmaster@Amazing-Animations.com).

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

**Disclaimer**

Our products and tutorials are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied. In no event shall we be liable for any damages including, but not limited to, direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages or other losses arising out of the use of or inability to use our products.

**Contact Us**

If you want to contact us, feel free to send us an email to: [webmaster@Amazing-Animations.com](mailto:webmaster@Amazing-Animations.com)
